She's a long way from home.
Anastasia: Once Upon a Time is a family, adventure,
fantasy film directed by Blake Harris.
Anastasia Romanov escapes through a portal when her family is threatened by Vladimir Lenin,
and she finds herself in the year 1988, befriended by a young American girl.
Czar Nicholas, played by Brandon Routh.
Anastasia, played by Emily Carey.
Megan, played by Amiah Miller.
Beatrice, played by Kendall Vertes.
Lily, played by Shanna Collins.
Vladimir Lenin, played by Jo Koy.
Anastasia: Once Upon a Time is a 2020 American fantasy adventure film very loosely
based on the legend of Grand Duchess Anastasia Nikolaevna of Russia.
The film stars Armando Gutierrez as Grigori Rasputin, Jo Koy as Vladimir Lenin,
Brandon Routh as Tsar Nicholas II and Emily Carey as Anastasia.
The film was released through digital platforms on April 7, 2020.